{
    "subject": "resource/Josh_Homme",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Wellwater_Conspiracy",
    "human_readable": "Josh Homme is associated with Wellwater Conspiracy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9704485535621643,
            "question": "Is Josh Homme involved in a band called Wellwater Conspiracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9668177962303162,
            "question": "What could be some reasons for Josh Homme to be associated with Wellwater Conspiracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9352236390113831,
            "question": "Is Wellwater Conspiracy a solo project by Josh Homme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9280379414558411,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the connection between Josh Homme and Wellwater Conspiracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9042981863021851,
            "question": "What genre of music is likely associated with Josh Homme and Wellwater Conspiracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154897093772888,
            "question": "What kind of project might Josh Homme and Wellwater Conspiracy be working on together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7798294425010681,
            "question": "Who is Josh Homme associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41865071654319763,
            "question": "What musical group is Wellwater Conspiracy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30097368359565735,
            "question": "Does Josh Homme have a history of collaborating with other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29550257325172424,
            "question": "Are there any other musical projects that Josh Homme is involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josh Homme is associated with Wellwater Conspiracy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7881_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Josh Homme have a history of collaborating with other artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7881_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical group is Wellwater Conspiracy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7881_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Josh Homme associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7881_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7881_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Matt, Ben and John McBain formed Wellwater Conspiracy in 1993. Additionally, it states that guest artists on Wellwater Conspiracy albums include Josh Homme, indicating his association with the band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}